pregnancy-calendars.net 2007-10-12

# Pregnancy Calendar Privacy Policy

Updated 7th September 2007

**Disclaimer:**  
We are not doctors or health professionals. Any material on Pregnancy-Calendars.Net is for information and entertainment purposes only. Material on our site should not take the place of a doctor or qualified professional.

**Liability:**  
You agree that your use of this website is at your sole risk. We do not warrant reliability of any statement or information displayed, distributed through or accessible from this website. As a convenience to you, we may provide links to websites operated by other entities, and you agree that we have no responsibility for information which is referenced or linked by this site. We are not responsible for any third party transactions via other websites users or advertisers or affiliates associated with Pregnancy-Calendars.Net.

If you have had an unsatisfactory transaction please resolve this directly with the third party. If you have had an unethical experience with one of our users, advertisers or affiliates please email us at feed.back@pregnancy-calendars.net and we will review the complaint and may remove them from our site in our sole discretion but we are not obligated to respond to your complaint. In the event that you have a dispute with one or more other users of this site or other persons or entities advertising on the site, you release Pregnancy-Calendars.Net from any claims, damages and demands of any kind and nature, known and unknown, arising out of or in any way connected with such disputes. You agree to indemnify and hold Pregnancy-Calendars.Net, Inc. harmless against all claims and expenses, including reasonable attorney’s fees, arising out of or related to your use of the Pregnancy-Calendars.Net site, violation of any law or regulation, violation of these terms and conditions, or violation of any proprietary or privacy right, or contracts formed with you through this site.

**Privacy Statement:**   
Pregnancy-Calendars.Net is dedicated to protecting your privacy.  You can visit our site without giving any information about yourself.  We do, however, require registration to post messages on our forums or to email or send private messages to members on our forums or to enter the members area of the site.  

**Information collected on Pregnancy-Calendars.Net:**

When you register to use the forums or the members area at Pregnancy-Calendars.Net we collect your email address and member name, your full name, due date, country and state.  We will use this to contact you periodically to announce site updates or if there is a violation of our terms of service.  You will also have the option to fill out a profile.  You can provide information such as your location, birthdate, instant messenger information or personal information about yourself.  Pregnancy-Calendars.Net also collects standard information for gathering statistics about your IP address, the browser you are using, the operating system on your computer, the site referring you to Pregnancy-Calendars.Net and the time you visited. 

**Use of cookies:**   
Pregnancy-Calendars.Net web site and forums do use cookies.  A cookie is placed on your computer to store information about the user.  Usage of cookies does not collect personal information about the user.  It is used to store your log in information so that you do not have to log in with each visit. 

**Use of your personal information:**   
Although we strive to protect your personal privacy, there are events in which we may need to disclose your personal information. Pregnancy-Calendars.Net may disclose your information if required to do so by law, if we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a legal proceeding against Pregnancy-Calendars.Net, or if it is necessary to protect copyrighted property of Pregnancy-Calendars.Net ****

**Users of our Forums must not:**   
Use vulgar language, any derogatory racial or religious comments, or any content that is illegal. We do not allow profanity on our forums. This includes disguised profanity. For example, the word b**ch is considered the same as posting the actual word. Any posts containing profanity will be edited or removed.

Post links to pornographic material. We do not allow pictures or links to pictures with nudity. (Exclusions include pictures of birth stories or pictures for educational purposes, must have prior approval from a moderator before posting).

Attack other members through posts on the board, email or private messages. We do not allow name calling, harassment or personal insults. You may express opposing view points but we want our members to feel safe from abuse. Please take the time to read your posts before you hit the post button and make sure that your posts are worded in a respectful nature. Posts that are not respectful, rude or insulting to other members will be removed.

Use our forums for recruiting members to other forums. This includes posts, emails, or pms saying “email me” or “instant message me” in the context of recruiting members to another forum. Pregnancy-Calendars.Net is an open community. Members are welcome to post on other sites but we do not allow members to use Pregnancy-Calendars.Net to poach members for another forum site. User must not post links to competing forums. You may post links to helpful articles or informational sites.

Pot stir or post disruptive posts on the forums. Pregnancy-Calendars.Net is a supportive community. We do not allow members to post disruptive posts on the forums. Any posts that are made simply to “stir the pot” or be disruptive will be removed.

**Troll on our forums:**  
We do not allow multiple accounts to be registered at Pregnancy-Calendars.Net. We do not allow impersonating another member’s identity, stealing photos from others, or fictitious posting.  
Post “mod/admin bashing” topics. Any topics insulting or antagonizing the moderation team at Pregnancy-Calendars.Net will be deleted. If you disagree with a moderation decision, you may send a respectful private message or email to an administrator expressing your concerns. If you choose to send profanity, personal insults, or any other abusive messages to an administrator or moderator your account will be permanently banned from Pregnancy-Calendars.Net. Pregnancy-Calendars.Net is a friendly community and we will not tolerate abuse of our staff. 

Post any spam, solicitations for money, charitable causes, or other products including diapers, formula, coupons, etc.  
Post research or journalism surveys on our forums.  
Post copyrighted material. If you have no personally written or created what is posted then do not post it. You can post links to articles or information.

When posting be aware that this is a public forum. Do not post personal information about yourself. If for some reason a member should choose to delete their account from Pregnancy-Calendars.Net, we will not be responsible for removing any pictures, posts, or other personal information from the forums.  
Post appropriate topics on our forums. We have a Heated Debates forum for controversial topics. Please post all debates on this forum. Controversial topics posted on other forums will be moved to the debate board or locked.

Although we do moderate our forums, we make no representations or warranties regarding the accuracy of any representations made and you agree that you will not hold us liable for any advice given or statements made via our message boards.

Pregnancy-Calendars.Net reserves the right to suspend members’ accounts who repeatedly violate our terms of service and to immediately discontinue, suspend, terminate or block users’ access to this site at any time.

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to correct any errors or omissions in any portion of the Pregnancy-Calendars.Net.com website.

**Copyright:**  
All materials on Pregnancy-Calendars.Net is copyrighted and Pregnancy-Calendars.Net retains ownership of all rights, title and interest in all copyrights in all documents, text, images created or owned by Pregnancy-Calendars.Net and displayed on this site. Do not reprint or reproduce any material for website or public use without permission from the owners of this site. You agree not to post or distribute on this site any information which infringes on a third party’s copyright or other proprietary rights.

Thank you for reviewing our terms of service.  Please check back periodically to see if there are any changes. If you have any questions concerning our terms of service or privacy policy please contact us at [_feed.back@pregnancy-calendars.net_](mailto:feed.back@pregnancy-calendars.net).
